<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Coding Days</string>

    <string name="day_1">Day 1</string>
    <string name="day_1_goal">Set up your development environment</string>
    <string name="day_1_description">This includes installing the necessary software and tools, such as a code editor, compiler, and debugger.</string>

    <string name="day_2">Day 2</string>
    <string name="day_2_goal">Learn the basics of programming syntax</string>
    <string name="day_2_description">This includes variables, data types, operators, and control flow statements.</string>

    <string name="day_3">Day 3</string>
    <string name="day_3_goal">Write your first program</string>
    <string name="day_3_description">This could be a simple program, such as a calculator or a text-based game.</string>

    <string name="day_4">Day 4</string>
    <string name="day_4_goal">Learn about functions and procedures</string>
    <string name="day_4_description">Functions allow you to group together code that performs a specific task. Procedures are similar to functions, but they do not return a value.</string>

    <string name="day_5">Day 5</string>
    <string name="day_5_goal">Learn about object-oriented programming (OOP)</string>
    <string name="day_5_description">OOP is a programming paradigm that uses objects to represent data and behavior.</string>

    <string name="day_6">Day 6</string>
    <string name="day_6_goal">Write a program that uses OOP principles</string>
    <string name="day_6_description">This could be a program to simulate a real-world system, such as a bank account or a library.</string>

    <string name="day_7">Day 7</string>
    <string name="day_7_goal">Learn about data structures</string>
    <string name="day_7_description">Data structures are ways of organizing data so that it can be accessed and manipulated efficiently.</string>

    <string name="day_8">Day 8</string>
    <string name="day_8_goal">Implement a data structure in code</string>
    <string name="day_8_description">This could be a simple data structure, such as a linked list or a stack.</string>

    <string name="day_9">Day 9</string>
    <string name="day_9_goal">Learn about algorithms</string>
    <string name="day_9_description">Algorithms are step-by-step instructions for solving a problem.</string>

    <string name="day_10">Day 10</string>
    <string name="day_10_goal">Implement an algorithm in code</string>
    <string name="day_10_description">This could be a simple algorithm, such as sorting or searching.</string>

    <string name="day_11">Day 11</string>
    <string name="day_11_goal">Learn about version control</string>
    <string name="day_11_description">Version control systems allow you to track changes to your code over time and revert to previous versions if necessary.</string>

    <string name="day_12">Day 12</string>
    <string name="day_12_goal">Create a new repository</string>
    <string name="day_12_description">To create a new repository on a version control service, you will need to create an account with the service and follow the instructions provided. Once you have created a repository, you can clone it to your local machine, add code to it, commit your changes, and push them to the remote repository.</string>

    <string name="day_13">Day 13</string>
    <string name="day_13_goal">Push your code</string>
    <string name="day_13_description">Pushing your code to the remote repository is a good way to keep your code safe and to share it with other developers. It is also a good way to collaborate on projects with other developers.</string>

    <string name="day_14">Day 14</string>
    <string name="day_14_goal">Create a new branch</string>
    <string name="day_14_description">Creating a new branch allows you to isolate your changes from the main branch of the repository. This is useful when you are working on a new feature or bug fix, as it allows you to experiment without breaking the main branch.</string>

    <string name="day_15">Day 15</string>
    <string name="day_15_goal">Make some changes</string>
    <string name="day_15_description">To make changes to your code, open the code file in a code editor or IDE and make the changes you need. Save the file and test your code to make sure the changes work as expected.</string>

    <string name="day_16">Day 16</string>
    <string name="day_16_goal">Commit your changes</string>
    <string name="day_16_description">Committing your changes regularly is a good way to keep track of your work and to create a history of your changes. It is also a good way to prepare for pushing your changes to a remote repository.</string>

    <string name="day_17">Day 17</string>
    <string name="day_17_goal">Create a pull request</string>
    <string name="day_17_description">To create a pull request (PR), make your changes on a separate branch and push them to the remote repository. Then, create a new pull request and explain your changes in the description. Once the PR is approved, merge it into the main branch.</string>

    <string name="day_18">Day 18</string>
    <string name="day_18_goal">Review the pull request</string>
    <string name="day_18_description">Reviewing pull requests is an important part of the software development process. By taking the time to review pull requests carefully, you can help to ensure that the code is high quality and that it meets the needs of the project.</string>

    <string name="day_19">Day 19</string>
    <string name="day_19_goal">Merge the pull request</string>
    <string name="day_19_description">Merging a pull request is the final step in the pull request workflow, and it results in the changes being made available to users. To merge a pull request, the developer who created it must first have all required approvals from other developers. Once the pull request is approved, the developer can merge it into the main branch.</string>

    <string name="day_20">Day 20</string>
    <string name="day_20_goal">Learn about testing</string>
    <string name="day_20_description">Testing is the process of checking whether your code works as expected.</string>

    <string name="day_21">Day 21</string>
    <string name="day_21_goal">Write a unit test</string>
    <string name="day_21_description">A unit test is a type of software test that verifies the functionality of a single unit of code, such as a function or class. Unit tests are typically written by developers and are run as part of the software development process.</string>

    <string name="day_22">Day 22</string>
    <string name="day_22_goal">Learn about integration testing</string>
    <string name="day_22_description">Integration testing is the process of testing how different parts of your code work together.</string>

    <string name="day_23">Day 23</string>
    <string name="day_23_goal">Write an integration test</string>
    <string name="day_23_description">Integration tests are important because they help to ensure that the different parts of a software system are working together as intended. Integration tests can also help to identify bugs that may not be found by unit tests.</string>

    <string name="day_24">Day 24</string>
    <string name="day_24_goal">Learn about regression testing</string>
    <string name="day_24_description">Regression testing is the process of testing your code to make sure that changes you have made have not introduced any new bugs.</string>

    <string name="day_25">Day 25</string>
    <string name="day_25_goal">Write a regression test</string>
    <string name="day_25_description">Regression tests are important because they help to ensure that the software system continues to work as intended after changes have been made.</string>

    <string name="day_26">Day 26</string>
    <string name="day_26_goal">Learn about deployment</string>
    <string name="day_26_description">Deployment is the process of making your code available to users.</string>

    <string name="day_27">Day 27</string>
    <string name="day_27_goal">Deploy your code</string>
    <string name="day_27_description">Deploying code is making your code available to users. This typically involves uploading your code to a server and configuring it to run.</string>

    <string name="day_28">Day 28</string>
    <string name="day_28_goal">Monitor your code</string>
    <string name="day_28_description">Monitoring code in production is the process of collecting and analyzing data about how your code is performing in a real-world environment. This data can be used to identify and fix bugs, improve performance, and ensure that your code is meeting the needs of your users.</string>

    <string name="day_29">Day 29</string>
    <string name="day_29_goal">Start a new coding project!</string>
    <string name="day_29_description">Choose a project you\'re passionate about, set realistic goals, and break it down into smaller tasks. Don\'t be afraid to ask for help, and have fun!.</string>
</resources>